<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Agency on Alter Ego 2</title>
    <link>/tags/agency/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Agency on Alter Ego 2</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/agency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Filter Traffic in GA4</title>
      <link>/posts/filter-traffic-in-ga4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/filter-traffic-in-ga4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used WordPress the most, setting up Google Analytics is easy with WordPress, thanks to the Google Site Kit plug-ins,&#xA;or any other plug-ins that can easily integrate with Google Analytics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the new goals in 2025 is to revamp my agency&amp;rsquo;s main &lt;a href=&#34;https://berlime.com&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; with entirely new stacks. Meaning&#xA;it does not run on WordPress like before, just for that sake of exploring more options and learn new things. More on that in another post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024</title>
      <link>/posts/2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;learned-a-lot&#34;&gt;Learned A Lot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024 was the most productive year. Ever since I got my agency incorporated in 2023, it somehow changed the way I work. I tend to do things much more careful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It opens up to how I approach things, from a whole new perspective to be sustainable and enough room to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many iterations of workflow templates, as I am wearing a lot of hats. Most of us would probably start hiring already at least getting freelancers to help out if not hiring on payroll.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Agency</title>
      <link>/posts/my-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/my-agency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there, this is the first blog post about my agency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I run a web design and development agency. I started out small by creating a website for my wedding business. This was before the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sole purpose to create a website for my wedding business is to seamlessly connect multiple providers and customers without having to communicate with me as a middle-man.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is a system I developed. The goal is to create &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.techtarget.com/searchcloudcomputing/definition/Software-as-a-Service&#34;&gt;an app a.k.a SaaS&lt;/a&gt; for everyone to use, basically a all in one web portal for weddings. This needs a lot of hours for research and development. I would probably scrap this idea for now as it is not practical for me and my agency at the moment. More on that some other time, keep a look-out at my &amp;ldquo;agency&amp;rdquo; tagged blog post for updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub</title>
      <link>/posts/github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/github/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-first-encounter-with-github&#34;&gt;My first encounter with GitHub&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All I knew about GitHub was some sort of place where you dump codes and make it available to the public. But still, I have no idea what is the purpose of it, at all. Until Tasnim, enlightened me what it really was.&#xA;See, of course I&amp;rsquo;ve watched a few YouTube videos of what GitHub is, I kind of get the idea but do not know how it works, what is it for, etcetera.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funnel</title>
      <link>/posts/funnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/funnel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-berlimes-funnel-tofu-aka-top-of-the-funnel&#34;&gt;First Berlime&amp;rsquo;s Funnel (TOFU &lt;em&gt;a.k.a Top Of the Funnel&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read more about Tofu &lt;a href=&#34;https://getwpfunnels.com/top-of-the-funnel/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. A funnel is basically a terminology used to generate leads. It is basically a way to filter through visitors or people that captures their attention into your business. Eventually turning them into paying visitors. It&amp;rsquo;s an abbreviation for &amp;ldquo;Top Of the Funnel&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, Tofu is exactly how it sounds like. We first bring people into the funnel which is the widest and &amp;rsquo;top&amp;rsquo; of the funnel. Which essentially what people see when they first enter your funnel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notion</title>
      <link>/posts/notion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/notion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;notionso---the-superpower-i-stumble-upon&#34;&gt;Notion.so - The Superpower I Stumble Upon&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notion is an app that you can decide on how do you want it to be. It is generally a note-taking app. On steroids, if you want it.&#xA;You can choose to make it as simple as a regular note-taking app, or you can also turn it into a &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;super app&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; like how I did, to run my agency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also run an internal finance insights for my agency. You see, having an accountant running a business is a must-have. Even when you subscribe a software to comply with the regulations. You still have some sort of limitation in manipulating your finance like setting aside budgets, create internal accounts for a certain category of stuffs. Well, Notion allows me to do that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NurusySyabab</title>
      <link>/posts/nurusysyabab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/nurusysyabab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-different-approach&#34;&gt;A different approach&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been using Elementor builder for a WordPress project. No doubt it is a great tool for me to start or in fact, anyone! This is the builder that I used when I first discovered WordPress. (The right way LOL) - &lt;em&gt;will definitely blog about this.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I quickly discovered that there are bunches of options you can include the tech-stack for your WordPress journey. Thanks to the nature of a technology, which tends to change/updates really fast. The theme that I used released a native &amp;lsquo;Full-Site Editing&amp;rsquo; experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
