<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backtracked on Alter Ego 2</title>
    <link>/tags/backtracked/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backtracked on Alter Ego 2</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/backtracked/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Agency</title>
      <link>/posts/my-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/my-agency/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello there, this is the first blog post about my agency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I run a web design and development agency. I started out small by creating a website for my wedding business. This was before the Covid-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sole purpose to create a website for my wedding business is to seamlessly connect multiple providers and customers without having to communicate with me as a middle-man.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is a system I developed. The goal is to create &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.techtarget.com/searchcloudcomputing/definition/Software-as-a-Service&#34;&gt;an app a.k.a SaaS&lt;/a&gt; for everyone to use, basically a all in one web portal for weddings. This needs a lot of hours for research and development. I would probably scrap this idea for now as it is not practical for me and my agency at the moment. More on that some other time, keep a look-out at my &amp;ldquo;agency&amp;rdquo; tagged blog post for updates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alter Ego 2 - First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/alter-ego-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/alter-ego-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was 16, I launched my blog site with blogpost.com (now blogger.com).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You say why I blog? Well, my parents did not manage to get a hold of a computer yet during that period. So what I did was, wrote a journal but wouldn’t call it a journal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You see, the way I did it was to write in a ‘magazine’ look and format where there will be so-called “ads” for the stuff I find interesting. There are 3 versions of this which will remain offline for keepsake and nostalgic moments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Delivery Rider</title>
      <link>/posts/food-delivery-rider/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/food-delivery-rider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-compare-between-working-full-time--being-a-food-delivery-rider-also-full-time&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s Compare Between Working Full-time &amp;amp; Being a Food Delivery Rider, Also Full Time&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Working as a Foodpanda food delivery rider for 21 days, which is the same as working full-time at about 7 to excluding lunch &amp;amp; small breaks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On average per day $100 * 21 days = $2100&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;operation-cost--&#34;&gt;Operation cost: -&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Meals: Around $6 per day (Eat in JB, 1 drink in SG). 6*21=126 &#xA;Petrol: $6 per day. 6*21=126 &#xA;Total operation cost: 126+126=336   &#xA;Take home cash: 2100-336=1764 &#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, this equals to a salary of $2624 working full-time with a take home cash of $2100 after deduction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notion</title>
      <link>/posts/notion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/notion/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;notionso---the-superpower-i-stumble-upon&#34;&gt;Notion.so - The Superpower I Stumble Upon&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notion is an app that you can decide on how do you want it to be. It is generally a note-taking app. On steroids, if you want it.&#xA;You can choose to make it as simple as a regular note-taking app, or you can also turn it into a &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;super app&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; like how I did, to run my agency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also run an internal finance insights for my agency. You see, having an accountant running a business is a must-have. Even when you subscribe a software to comply with the regulations. You still have some sort of limitation in manipulating your finance like setting aside budgets, create internal accounts for a certain category of stuffs. Well, Notion allows me to do that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NurusySyabab</title>
      <link>/posts/nurusysyabab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/nurusysyabab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-different-approach&#34;&gt;A different approach&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been using Elementor builder for a WordPress project. No doubt it is a great tool for me to start or in fact, anyone! This is the builder that I used when I first discovered WordPress. (The right way LOL) - &lt;em&gt;will definitely blog about this.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I quickly discovered that there are bunches of options you can include the tech-stack for your WordPress journey. Thanks to the nature of a technology, which tends to change/updates really fast. The theme that I used released a native &amp;lsquo;Full-Site Editing&amp;rsquo; experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room Updates</title>
      <link>/posts/room-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/room-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ever since my late mom bought the house I currently live in, it is still in the original, unadorned state. My late mom did not opt for any renovations or even fancy decorations and pieces of furniture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only thing that my mom did was the kitchen cabinet and countertop which was not included when we got this house.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah, we got it first-hand, brand-new back in around 2014.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
