<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Alter Ego 2</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Alter Ego 2</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rounded Corners</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/rounded-corners/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/rounded-corners/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="wcpa-rounded-corners-for-custom-wood-orders">WCPA Rounded corners for custom wood orders&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>First, we need to determine the minmax of the cuts for each corner. This cuts must be relative to the width and the length.
The goal is to allow users to customize order not just by adding rounded corners on the required sides, but also, allows granular measurement for irregular shapes, and routing.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="we-need-to-start-from-the-4-sided-measurements">We need to start from the 4 sided measurements&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>First, we need to identify the mid-point variable where,&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Free Up Space Ubuntu</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/free-up-space-ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/free-up-space-ubuntu/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="1-clear-the-apt-cache">1. Clear the APT Cache&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Find out how large is the apt package cache:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>du -sh /var/cache/apt/archives
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>Clear the cache:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>sudo apt-get clean
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;h2 id="2-remove-old-kernels">2. Remove Old Kernels&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Not sure how it works, really but here we go,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Proceed with caution:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>sudo apt-get autoremove --purge
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;h2 id="3-last-stay-up-to-date">3. Last, stay up to date&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Do this regularly&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>sudo apt update &amp;amp;&amp;amp; upgrade
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>You can read the full article where I found the above commands &lt;a href="https://www.omgubuntu.co.uk/2016/08/5-ways-free-up-space-on-ubuntu">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>LTeX- Spell Checker</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/ltex-spell-checker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/ltex-spell-checker/</guid><description>&lt;p>So ni kire dia sync?&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;em>Post Changelogs&lt;/em>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;em>16th Dec 2024 - Updated Hugo Version&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;em>15th Aug 2024 - Publish Date&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item><item><title>WCPA Circle Shape</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/wcpa-circle-shape/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 20:47:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/wcpa-circle-shape/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="planning">Planning&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>We will now strategise and plan how to execute the WCPA fields based on each product and it&amp;rsquo;s variations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Below is what we need to accomplish&lt;/p>
&lt;table>
 &lt;thead>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;th>Syntax&lt;/th>
 &lt;th>Description&lt;/th>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;/thead>
 &lt;tbody>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>Header&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Title&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>Paragraph&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>Text&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table></description></item><item><title>Github</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/github/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/github/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="my-first-encounter-with-github">My first encounter with Github&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>All I knew about GitHub was some sort of place where you dump codes and make it available to the public. But still, I have no idea what is the purpose of it, at all. Until Tasnim, enlightened me what it really was.
See, of course I&amp;rsquo;ve watched a few YouTube videos of what GitHub is, I kind of get the idea but do not know how it works, what is it for, etcetera.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>White Loaf</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/white-loaf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 00:35:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/white-loaf/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="sour-dough">Sour Dough&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>My wife recently is interested to make her own sourdough, thanks to B.E.N (You can refer to the post I talk about B.E.N, a grocery store. Click &lt;a href="https://alterego.berlime.com/posts/ben/">Here&lt;/a>) Sourdough have a lot of variety, types, shape, taste &amp;amp; purpose.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I recommend Goat Cheese Sandwhich to go with. It is a classic sandwhich that consists of a slice of sour dough, a thick slice of goat cheese, drizzle with olive oil and season it with some salt and black pepper. Toast it for about 5 minutes, and for the extra touch, blow torch the top surface to have some smoked/charred taste. Or if you somehow have a &lt;a href="https://www.webstaurantstore.com/guide/969/what-is-a-salamander-oven.html">salamander&lt;/a>, a cooking equipment.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SEO Partnership</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/seo-partnership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 22:46:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/seo-partnership/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="new-seo-service">New SEO Service&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Today marks the journey of introducing a new suite of services to my agency. Before we dive in, let me tell you a story about why offering SEO services may not be as easy as spinning up a new product line. You see, running an agency has its own challenges, especially with limited resources in terms of manpower and financial capabilities. My agency&amp;rsquo;s core product offers a web development service. This service alone involves thousands of technicalities that require a certain level of skillset.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Alter Ego 2 - First Post</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/alter-ego-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/alter-ego-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>When I was 16, I launched my blog site with blogpost.com (now blogger.com).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You say why I blog? Well, my parents did not manage to get a hold of a computer yet during that period. So what I did was, wrote a journal but wouldn’t call it a journal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You see, the way I did it was to write in a ‘magazine’ look and format where there will be so-called “ads” for the stuff I find interesting. There are 3 versions of this which will remain offline for keepsake and nostalgic moments.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Food Delivery Rider</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/food-delivery-rider/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/food-delivery-rider/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="lets-compare-between-working-full-time--being-a-food-delivery-rider-also-full-time">Let&amp;rsquo;s Compare Between Working Full-time &amp;amp; Being a Food Delivery Rider, Also Full Time&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Working as a Foodpanda food delivery rider for 21 days, which is the same as working full-time at about 7 to excluding lunch &amp;amp; small breaks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On average per day $100 * 21 days = $2100&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="operation-cost--">Operation cost: -&lt;/h3>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>Meals: Around $6 per day (Eat in JB, 1 drink in SG). 6*21=126 
Petrol: $6 per day. 6*21=126 
Total operation cost: 126+126=336 
Take home cash: 2100-336=1764 
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>So, this equals to a salary of $2624 working full-time with a take home cash of $2100 after deduction.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>I use Hugo for this blog.</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/hugo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 20:37:34 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/hugo/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hugo-is-a-static-site-generator">Hugo is a static site generator.&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Introduced by my good friend of mind back in Secondary school. I straight away fell in love in static sites. I have been dabbling into WordPress thinking that it is the Holy Grail of web development. &lt;em>buzzz!!&lt;/em> nope. I was totally wrong.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tasnim, actually first started using Hugo for his own personal blog. He thought me a lot about how VSCODE works, he is darn good at explaining complex things into simple terms. Which struck me like a lightning.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>B.E.N!</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/ben/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/ben/</guid><description>&lt;p>I live in Johor Bahru, Malaysia. Specifically, Western part of Johor. Near Legoland Malaysia.
In my area, there aren&amp;rsquo;t many groceries store around, there about 6 supermarkets nearby (at least 10-30 mins). Further than that, I do not consider it nearby.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>6 supermarkets may sound a lot for some. But not to me because most of them sell the same things. Say for an example, I could not find any natural sea salt in most of the supermarket.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Notion</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/notion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 23:25:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/notion/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="notionso---the-superpower-i-stumble-upon">Notion.so - The Superpower I Stumble Upon&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Notion is an app that you can decide on how do you want it to be. It is generally a note taking app. On steroids, if you want it.
You can choose to make it as simple as a regular note taking app, or you can also turn it into a &lt;em>&amp;ldquo;super app&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em> like how I did, to run my agency.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I also run an internal finance insights for my agency. You see, having an accountant running a business is a must have. Even when you subscribe a software to comply with the regulations. You still have some sort of limitation in manipulating your finance like setting aside budgets, create internal accounts for a certain category of stuffs. Well, Notion allows me to do that.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Funnel</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/funnel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 13:08:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/funnel/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Original Post date: 19th June 2024.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="first-berlimes-funnel-tofu-aka-top-of-the-funnel">First Berlime&amp;rsquo;s Funnel (TOFU &lt;em>a.k.a Top Of the Funnel&lt;/em>)&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>You can read more about Tofu &lt;a href="https://getwpfunnels.com/top-of-the-funnel/">here&lt;/a>. A funnel is basically a terminology used to generate leads. It is basically a way to filter through visitors or people that captures their attention into your business. Eventually turning them into paying visitors.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So, Tofu is exactly how it sounds like. We first bring people into the funnel which is the widest part of the funnel. The wide part of the funnel, is called &amp;rsquo;top of the funnel&amp;quot;. Which essentially what people see when they first enter your funnel.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Nurusysyabab</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/nurusysyabab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 20:25:16 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/nurusysyabab/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="a-different-approach">A different approach&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I have been using Elementor builder for a WordPress project. No doubt it is a great tool for me to start or in fact, anyone! This is the builder that I used when I first discovered WordPress. (The right way LOL) - &lt;em>will definitely blog about this.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I quickly discovered that there are bunch of options you can include the tech-stack for your WordPress journey. Thanks to the nature of a technology, which tends to change/updates really fast. The theme that I used realesed a native &amp;lsquo;Full-Site Editing&amp;rsquo; experience.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>WP Meet Up</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/wp-meet-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 22:56:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/wp-meet-up/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello there! Before we start on the topic. This is the first backtracked post. It was a draft I while developing this new Hugo site.
Let me bring you back in time. The post date you see above is the event or the moment happened. The real date that I post a backtracked blog is under &amp;ldquo;Published Date&amp;rdquo; (See example below)&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;em>Changelog&lt;/em>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;em>Publish Date: 19th June 2024&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;em>Restructure: 21th June 2024&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>The changelog(s) will be&lt;em>grayed out&lt;/em> and placed in the bottom of every blog post. With added a little bit of context what are the changes is made to the particular posts.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Agency</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/my-agency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 13:08:31 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/my-agency/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Original Post date: 12th May 2024&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Hello there, this is the first post that I will be sharing about my agency.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I run a web design and development agenncy. I started out small by creating a website for my wedding business. This was before the Covid-19 pandemic.
My sole purpose to create a website for my wedding business is to seamlessly connect multiple providers with customers without having to communicate with me the wedding planner.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Room Updates</title><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/room-updates/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 16:51:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/room-updates/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Original Post date: 13th May 2024&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Ever since my late mom bought the house I currently live in, it is still in the original, unadorned state. My late mom did not opt for any renovations or even fancy decorations and pieces of furniture.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The only thing that my mom did was the kitchen cabinet and countertop which was not included when we got this house.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Oh yeah, we got it first-hand, brand new back in around 2014.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/untitled/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alterego2.vercel.app/posts/untitled/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>